Wait.
稍等。
&gt;&gt; What's wrong?
&gt;&gt; 怎么了？
&gt;&gt; When did this turn into a cooking show all of a sudden?
&gt;&gt; 这怎么突然变成烹饪节目了？
&gt;&gt; Since we had to talk about methods?
&gt;&gt; 因为我们得解说方法不？
&gt;&gt; Care to explain, Rachael Ray?
&gt;&gt; 能解释吗，Rachael Ray？
&gt;&gt; [LAUGH] Well, have you ever baked a cake before?
&gt;&gt; [笑声] 你有烘烤蛋糕的经验吗？
&gt;&gt; I have eaten a cake before.
&gt;&gt; 我吃过蛋糕。
&gt;&gt; Okay.
&gt;&gt; 好吧。
Well, then you're fully qualified for this.
那你完全能胜任这一点。
&gt;&gt; Okay.
&gt;&gt; 好。
&gt;&gt; All you have to do to bake a cake is to put in flour, sugar.
&gt;&gt; 你只需放入面粉和糖。
&gt;&gt; The ingredients.
&gt;&gt; 烘烤成分。
Okay.
对。 &gt;&gt; 那些成分。
Yeah.
是的。
And then you follow the instructions of the recipe.
然后你照着食谱上的指示。
&gt;&gt; Okay. &gt;&gt; And then out comes a cake.
&gt;&gt; 是。 &gt;&gt; 然后蛋糕就完成了。
&gt;&gt; Like this?
&gt;&gt; 就这样？
&gt;&gt; Yeah.
&gt;&gt; 是呀。
&gt;&gt; Okay. Well
&gt;&gt; 好吧。
connect the analogy to the methods one more time.
再把比喻和方法连接起来。
&gt;&gt; Okay. Sure so for
&gt;&gt; 好的，没问题。
a method you can put in inputs.
在一个方法中，你可输入数据。
&gt;&gt; Like we did the quantity for the display method?
&gt;&gt; 就像我们在显示方法中做的数量？
&gt;&gt; Yeah, and then you execute the instructions of the method.
&gt;&gt; 是的，接着你执行该指示。
&gt;&gt; Okay, almost like the recipe for making a cake?
&gt;&gt; 好，就好像烘培蛋糕的食谱？
&gt;&gt; Mm-hm.
&gt;&gt; 嗯。
Then you can have the output value returned.
然后你会有输出值回流。
&gt;&gt; Outputs, they are delicious.
&gt;&gt; 输出值，真美味。
&gt;&gt; [LAUGH] &gt;&gt; Let's look up more information
&gt;&gt; [笑声] &gt;&gt; 让我们来看看更多
about input parameters for methods.
关于输入方法参数的资料。
I'm going to do a Google search for Jjava method parameter.
我打算到谷歌搜索Java方法的参数。
The first link looks good so I'm going to click on it.
第一个链接看起来不错，我要点击一下。
Now this article talks about passing information to a method.
这篇文章谈到传递信息的方法。
Here's a code snippet that computes the monthly payments for a home loan.
这里有个用于计算每月支付住房贷款的代码片断。
It has four input parameters, loan amount, interest rate, future value
它有4个得输入的参数，贷款金额，利息率，未来贷款的收益
of the loan, as well as the number periods of the length of the loan.
以及贷款期限。
And then inside this method we see that we can use these input parameters
通过这方法我们能够用这些
simply as variables to do our math calculations.
简单的参数作为我们算法的变量。
When we call the compute payment method,
当我们调用贷款支付方法时,
we have to make sure we pass in the inputs in this specific order.
我们得确保依据特定的顺序输入参数。
So the loan amount has to go first, and then the rate and so on.
因此得先输入贷款金额，然后利息率等。
For the quiz in this section,
此部分的测验中，
you'll have the chance to review this article in more detail.
你可以更详细的阅读这篇文章。
Within the main activity of the desk Java app,
在Java应用程序的主要活动，
we're going to be modifying the display quantity method and
我们将以修改显示数量的方法和
the input parameter to give you some practice.
输入的参数作为你的练习。
Notice that in the decrement method of our app,
注意在应用程序中的减量法,
what we call the display quantity method,
我们所称为显示参数的方法，
we're passing the quantity variable over as input to this method.
我们把数量变成方法的输入参数。
But the input parameter is called 'number', so
但这些参数被称为“号码”，
whenever we want to refer to this input, we just have to say number.
所以当我们要引用这参数，我们只需说出它的号码。
Now technically we could have used the global quantity variable within this
现今，我们可在这方法上使用
method instead of passing it as an input parameter.
全球数量而不是将它变成方法的输入参数。
but for the purposes of teaching you about input parameters,
但为了教学目的,
let's just leave it like this.
就让它留着吧。
I can change this call to the display quantity method so
我可把这对话变成显示数量的方法
it passes input, the number 30.
所以输入后，它变成30。
This is valid because it still matches the input data type.
这是有效的，因为它仍是输入数据的类型。
So in the decrement method when we call it display quantity,
于是在减量法时,我们把它称为显示的数量,
it will jump down here and it will execute these instructions, and
它会跳到这儿，然后执行这些指示,
the variable number will have the value of 30.
然后这些变量将会变成30。
I'll run it on my device to show you, so now when I run the minus button on my
我向你展示在我的手机里的设置，当我在程序上
app, it will display a quantity of 30 here.
执行减量,它将在这显示数量为30。
So let me try that.
让我尝试。
There. And it actually happened like that.
这。它真的是这样的。
I can also create a different variable and pass that as an input to the method.
我也可以创建一个不同的变量并将其作为一种输入的方法。
Here I've created a local variable called some quantity, and
在这里，我创建了一个定量，接着
I initialized it to 100.
我把它的初期值设为100。
I passed this variable as input to this method,
我把这这变量输入引用于该方法中，
and now the number variable inside here has a value of 100.
现在该变量值100。
Let me run this on the device.
让我执行这例子。
Now I expect when I hit the minus button the quantity will update to 100.
现在我估计当我点击减号按钮时，该数量将更新为100。
And it does.
确实是这样。
These are just some things you can do to experiment with
这都是一些你可以用来做实验的事情
passing in different inputs to a method.
通过方法不同的输入。
As you work with input parameters,
当你使用输入的参数,
another term that you might come across is arguments.
你可能会遇到另个术语称为论据。
When you call a method,
当你调用一个方法时，
the inputs being passed to that method are called the arguments.
输入的参数被传递的被称为论据。
Now this is kind of a funny word.
这是有点有趣的词语。
Because when you think of arguments, you think of people yelling and
因为arguments（争吵），你会想到大呼小叫
cursing at each other.
甚至互相咒骂着。
But this is not like that.
但并非如此。
Arguments are simply the inputs being passed to a method.
Arguments （论据）是输入的参数被传为方法。
Input parameters are the actual inputs in your method declaration and
输入参数是方法声明中的实际的参数
those are the variables that are used within your method.
这些是你使用的方法中的变数。
So that's a slight difference between input parameter and arguments.
所以输入的参数和论据是略有区别的。
In any case, go ahead and read the article and
无论如何，你可以阅读该文章
the instructor notes about method parameters.
这教员有记载关于方法的参数。
Then go ahead and experiment with the code in your app.
然后继续在你的应用程序中尝试这代码。
First try to rename the number input parameter
首先先尝试重命名输入数字的参数
within the display quantity method declaration.
于显示数量方法声明。
Just simply give it a different variable name.
只需简单地给它一个不同的变量名称。
Then go ahead and fix any errors, and then run the app again.
然后修复任何错误，再重新运行该应用程序。
For the next test, go ahead and change the data type
在接下来的测试，试图改变输入数据的类型
of the number input parameter from an int to something else like String.
像是从整数变成其他类型如 String。
Observe what happens and then go ahead and undo the change.
观察结果然后撤消更改。
If you want to experiment with other things, go right ahead.
如果你想试验其他的，请便。
For example, if you have a question,
例如若你有一个问题，
what would happen if I do x, then just go ahead and try it.
如果我做X，会发生什么事？尽管去尝试。